<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anton Official</title>
    <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anton Official</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© T. Anton Puolakka</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 14:12:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>To all dear MeetFrank people</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/posts/3-mf/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 14:12:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/posts/3-mf/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I am open for business.
The last few years I&#39;ve been involved with many IoT projects. Not super-small-scale embedded but reasonably powerful devices that can do a variety of tricks. Combined with cloud tools we see the value, a non-trivial value indeed.
Python 3, JavaScript/Node, Java 2 SE and last but not least: C++/STL. Experienced data modeler and DB administrator. For IoT the of the breed is Balena, just got to love it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Retrospect</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/posts/2-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 13:11:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/posts/2-learned/</guid>
      <description>The course was passed. More importantly, it was quite fun. It is good to get the grade but the journey alone was even better.
Student 028 Learned  That Aalto takes it easy with deadlined and project deliverables while imposing super-strict deadline policy on the students. Some deep git stuff (that I do not remember but I have a hint that it exists now) That the videos talk about waterfall style in such a way that it&#39;s value is not well understood (V model is good and justified, guys, but not necessarily on your ecommerce site!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aalto DevOps Experience: Why?</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/posts/1-thiscourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 13:07:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/posts/1-thiscourse/</guid>
      <description>Learned about FiTech somewhere early September 2019 and happily started to cherry-pick courses from various universities including Aalto.
While I&#39;ve been professionally involved with software engineering for more than a quarter of a century I&#39;ve seen the gradual change in the software realization process. I must admit Scrum made a bigger impact than any other system and not least because I was trained to the drill by people who participated writing Agile Manifesto and defining the Scrum process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let me introduce myself</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:05:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-028-advanced/about/</guid>
      <description>The name is Anton Puolakka and in the professional world I am a digital strategist who can and has to deal with issues related to ISO OSI layers ranging from 3 to 8.
The current domain in which I am applying my skills in is electric boating. The expected impact is no less than to revolutionarize how free-time recreational boating shall be felt.
In historical context I have experienced a technologial journey with some true evolution: decades ago I needed to set up an endless cluster of raw socket options to get me connected right while quite recently the maturity has reached a level that I can set up a working web server with one single line of code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>